xgenseo.com 2012-06-30

# XGenSEO - SEO Tools and Social Marketing Software - Privacy Policy

At Apex Pacific, your privacy and security are extremely important to us. We want you feel confident visiting our websites and using our products. This page explains the type of information that we collect, how such information is used and under what circumstances and to whom it may be disclosed. 

**_1\. Collection of Personal Information:_**

In order to better serve our customers and those interested in our products and services, Apex Pacific may collect personal and non-personal information through our website. Our website uses forms for information requests and orders. Contact information from all forms (including name, address, email address, payment information, registration information etc.) is used to process and deliver orders and mail information about our company to our customers. We will not sell, share, or rent any of this information with any other person or company. Any financial information our customers submit, such as credit card details is used only to charge the customers for the products and services they are purchasing.   
If a user decideds to use our "Tell A Friend" application for forwarding a Serious Magic e-mail to their friend or informing a friend about our website, we ask them for the friend's name and e-mail address. Serious Magic will automatically send the friend the specified e-mail or the specified website information. Serious Magic will not use the friend's information to contact them in the future. 

_**2\. Use of Personal Information**_

We use your personal information in the following ways: to tell you about products and services available on our website; to obtain your feedback in regards to our products and services and overall customer satisfaction; to fulfill requests you submitted, to process your orders, to send you our free monthly newsletter and promotional materials we think may be of interest.   
If you do not wish to receive any of these communications from us, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each message, or by sending an email to: unsubscribe@apexpacific.com. 

**_3\. Security of Personal Information_**

We make every effort to protect your personal identifiable information. All secure orders and confidential information are processed through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology via secure server. All customer contact information including credit card number and name and address is guarded with the utmost security and discretion. 

**_4\. Third party sharing_**

We will not sell, share, or rent any of your personal information with any third party.   
Sometimes we may partner with other companies and individuals so that they can assist us in servicing you (such as providing customer services such as technical support). Such companies and individuals will have access to the personal information needed to perform these functions, and are strictly prohibited from using it for any other purposes.   
We may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that disclosure is legally required, or in order to protect our rights. 

**_5\. Use of Cookies_**

A cookie is a small text file of information that a web site transfers to an user's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're on a website. The use of cookies is an industry standard, we also use them so that we can better serve you when you return to our website. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

**_6\. Links_**

The Apex Pacific website contains links to other Websites. Apex Pacific Pty Ltd is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites; their privacy practices may differ from ours.
